It has been something sudden what is known about
ha sido algo repentino lo que se sabe de
the daughter of Anabel Pantoja and Anabel
la hija de Anabel Pantoja y Anabel
Pantoja admitted to the UI at 40 days
Pantoja ingresada en la ui a sus 40 días
old Well it's 52 but 10 days more
de vida Bueno son 52 pero 10 días más
than less that is known for nothing It's that
que menos que se sabe por nada Es que
these are taking out articles just for the sake of it okay
estos son sacar artículos por sacar vale
the seriousness of the situation has
la gravedad de la situación ha
mobilized the Pantoja family
movilizado a la familia Pantoja está
everyone is very very involved very
todo el mundo muy muy volcado muy
worried eh Antonio Rossi let's see what
preocupado eh Antonio Rossi a ver qué ha
Antonio Rossi has said Antonio Rossi
dicho Antonio Rossi Antonio Rossi
explained that the first contact with the
explicó que el primer contacto con los
doctors occurred on Wednesday when the
médicos ocurrió el miércoles cuando los
parents took the girl to the emergency room when they
padres llevaron a la niña a urgencia al
noticed that something was not right on Thursday the
notar que algo no iba bien el jueves la
family was informed of the situation
familia fue informada de la situación
Including Isabel Pantoja however it
Incluyendo a Isabel Pantoja sin embargo
was on Friday when Alma's condition
fue el viernes cuando la condición de
worsened
Alma empeoró
significantly which led the
significativamente lo que llevó a la
family to move to the
familia a trasladarse de emergencia a
Canary Islands man what what will it be
Canarias tío qué qué será de forma
suddenly and a worsening
repentina y un empeoramiento
any infection or something like that
cualquier infección o algo por el estilo
or I mean whatever it is it has to
o sea es que lo que sea lo que sea tiene
be something whatever it is it has to be something
que se algo lo que sea tiene que se algo
that wasn't there before And now it
que antes no estaba Y que ahora
's [ __ ] how bad it makes my body eh
está [__] que mal me pone el cuerpo eh
how bad it makes my body the truth is I don't
qué mal me pone el cuerpo la verdad no
know if  The same thing happens to you eh but for me
sé si os pasa lo mismo eh pero yo es que
these things about children make me feel
estas cosas de los niños me ponen me
really bad,
ponen me ponen muy mal la
really, really, really upset. Let's see if today there's something that we can
verdad A ver si hoy toca cosit que nos
laugh a little bit later but for me
riamos un poquito luego pero yo es que
these things make me feel a little bit, I do
estas cosas me dejan un poquito
n't know, I don't know, I mean, on
es que no sé es que no sé o sea el
Wednesday, Wednesday, Wednesday they
miércoles el miércoles el miércoles
saw
vieron
bronchitis I don't want to speculate, I don't
bronquitis Es que no quiero especular no
want to speculate because
quiero especular porque
speculating, yes, there will be some little thing Look,
especular sí será alguna cosita Mira
Merchi, Anel Pantoja's mother. Let's see,
merchi la madre de Anel Pantoja A ver
let's see a little bit, let's
vamos a ver vamos a ver un poquito el el
see if there's a little more
a ver si hay un poquito más de
calm, Pantoja's mother arrives at the
tranquilidad la madre Pantoja llega al
Maternal and Child Hospital in Gran
hospital materno infantil de Gran
Canaria to be with her.
canaria para estar junto a su
Hi, there's
Hi hay
concern
preocupación
of of of
of of
a strong urinary infection, it could
of una infección de urina fuerte puede
be, being so little, I don't know, the
ser siendo tan pequeñitos no sé la
truth is that if we play guessing,
verdad es que si jugamos a la adivinanza
family. I mean, until they say anything, the
familia Yo hasta que no digan nada la
truth is that we should. Not speculate, we're
verdad que deberíamos No especular
just going to be on the
simplemente vamos a vamos a estar
lookout and of course, as soon as there's
pendiente y por supuesto en el momento
news, but we're
que haya una noticia pero estamos
talking about 99:10, today there's not going to
hablando de que son las 99:10 ya hoy no
be anything either, eh, but no, it doesn't
va a haber nada tampoco eh pero no no
look good, eh, it's not
pinta bien
looking good, family  To be honest To be
eh No pinta bien familia Siendo sincero
honest I hope I'm wrong it doesn't
Siendo sincero ojalá me equivoque no
look good because if from Wednesday
pinta bien porque si desde el miércoles
until now we're not talking about it Hey
hasta ahora no que estamos hablando Oye
what the [ __ ] are we doing man I don't know what day I'm
a qué [__] estamos tío no sé en el día
living in it's Monday okay I mean it's
que vivo estamos a lunes vale o sea han
been a few days now and if from
pasado Ya unos cuantos de días y si del
Wednesday until now there hasn't been any improvement yes yes there was
miércoles a ahora no ha habido mejoría
a little improvement at
si si hubiese un poco de mejoría por lo
least Hey well it was whatever it was and it was
menos Oye pues ha sido lo que sea y ha
very serious but there's a little
sido muy grave pero va habiendo un poco
improvement and then today well the
de mejoría Y entonces hoy pues tiene la
thing is the girl is still a little bit sick
cosa está malita la chiquilla todavía
but well it's under control Okay so
pero bueno está controlada Vale pues
then maybe grandma would have a
entonces a lo mejor la abuela tendría
different face and she would say to the press thank you thank you I'm
otra cara y le diría a la prensa gracias
not going to tell you anything since it
gracias no os voy a decir nada ya que
's An Verel who has to say you
sea an verel la que tenga que decir
know but she doesn't look well she does
sabes pero es que no tiene buena cara es
n't look well she doesn't look well it's
que no tiene buena cara es que no tiene
that here she is her soul is broken
est que aquí está está el alma partida
eh her soul is
eh está el alma
broken they get through very serious things
rota salen adelante de cosas gravísima
listen to me man Well I hope it is I hope
hazme caso hombre Pues ojalá sará ojalá
for God because honestly look I have
por Dios porque de verdad que mira que
n't even met her I've never spoken to
no la conozco nunca hablado la vida con
An B But the truth is that these things
an B Pero la verdad es que estas cosas
make me very bad they make me very bad
me ponen muy mal que me ponen muy mal la
true marquise I haven't taken that into account
verdad marquesa yo no hecho cuenta en
and really marquise are you
eso y de verdad marquesa estás
sending us WhatsApp I've seen you in the
mandándonos WhatsApp te he visto en el
chat I don't know if I've seen you in
chat No sé si te he visto en el chat de
other youtubers' chat I don't know if it was
otros youtubers no sé si ha sido de
Albert de Diego's which one but I've
Albert de Diego de cuál de ellos pero te
seen you in another youtuber's chat I've
he visto en el chat de otro youtuber te
seen you tagging several youtubers
he visto etiquetando a varios youtubers
and I've seen you sending us WhatsApp
y te he visto mandándonos WhatsApp
So I don't know what you mean by
Entonces no sé a qué te refieres con
here it's already
aquí ya se ha
leaked right man please
filtrado verdad hombre por favor
qua a little bit
qua un poquito
about Raquel Good morning I'm simply going to
de Raquel Buenos días simplemente
ask about
preguntara de
Anabel such a delicate situation that they're
Anabel tan delicado que están
going through have you spoken to her spoken
viviendo has hablado con ella hablado
to anyone in the family with is I'd
con alguien de la familia con is
rather not comment on anything really it's
prefiero no comentar nada de verdad es
very delicate everything just
muy delicado todo simplemente
calm down
tranquilizarnos está todo el
everyone is there Isabel to you thanks
mundo que está Isabel a ti gracias
well Raquel What V to
bueno Raquel Qué V a
say that it doesn't look good
decir que no pinta bien
eh it doesn't look
eh que no pinta
good let's see we spoke with Sonia Cervant
bien a ver hablamos con Sonia cervant
psychologist who explains to us how
psicóloga que nos Explica cómo deben
first-time parents should face a
afrontar unos padres primerisos un
critical moment like the one
momento crítico como el que están
Anabel is going through And how to face it doesn't matter
viviendo Anabel Y cóm afrontar da un
what they tell you It's
poco igual lo que te digan
not that there's nothing else it's that there's nothing else
No es que no hay más nada
Adela González
es que no hay más nada Adela González se
speaks out about Anabel Pantoja  with this
pronuncia sobre Anabel Pantoja con este
message a
mensaje un abrazo
huge hug Look at grandma's face,
enorme Que fíjate la cara de la abuela
eh, it's like if she were here Although the
eh es que si estuviera Aunque está la
little girl is obviously sick, but if she
chiquilla mala evidentemente pero si
were, things were more under control, I
estuviera la cosa más más controlada yo
think her face would be a
creo que la cara sería el semblante un
little more
poquito más de
calm, you know And it's that you
tranquilidad sabes Y es
know,
que es que sabes
the panelist Kiko Hernández shows
el tertuliano Kiko Hernández se
solidarity with Anabel Pantoja and understands
solidariza con Anabel Pantoja y entiende
her pain because it reminds him of his own
su dolor porque le recuerda su propia
experience, he reveals that his daughters
experiencia desvela que sus hijas
spent three months in the UI after being
estuvieron tres meses en la ui después
born Of course, but after being
de nacer Claro pero después de
born, eh, the thing is, she's another marquise
nacer eh el tema es que es otra marquesa
Ah Sorry, marquise Sorry, marquise, forgive me, forgive me,
Ah Perdona marquesa Perdona marquesa
marquise, there's
perdóname perdóname marquesa es que hay
a certain marquise who won't stop
una tal marquesa que no para de
writing to me on WhatsApp and I've seen her
escribirme por el WhatsApp y la he visto
on a few YouTubers
ya por el de unos cuantos de youtubers
who wants to break news, wants to
que quiere dar una noticia que quiere
break leaked news, well, let's see, La
dar una noticia filtrada bueno a ver La
Movida, eh Sorry, eh, marquise, if it's not
Movida eh Perdona eh marquesa si no eres
you, please rectify it, okay, okay,
tú por favor rectifica vale vale
marquise, don't, don't get angry, these are
marquesa no te no te enfades es que son
very delicate moments, I have to be
momentos muy delicados me tengo que
very serious Forgive me,
poner muy serio Perdóname
eh Let's see  let's go if Listen
eh A ver vamos a si Escuchar El cli de
Marta riesco's cli that it seems that she
Marta riesco que que parece que también
has also said something to her Look Anabel
le ha dicho algo Mira Anabel
Pantoja Ana Rosa
Pantoja Ana Rosa
Belén Esteban is absent from her work
Belén Esteban se ausenta de su trabajo
for
por
Anabel this is how María Patiño protected
Anabel así protegió María Patiño a la
Anabel Pantoja's daughter
hija de Anabel
a room enabled for
Pantoja una sala habilitada para los
family members there is no evolution neither for
familiares no hay evolución ni para
better nor for worse
mejor ni para peor
Isabel Pantoja has no return date
Isabel Pantoja no tiene fecha de regreso
and is with her brother
y se encuentra junto a su hermano
Agustín in Las Palmas de Gran Canaria
Agustín en Las Palmas de Gran canaria
since this weekend she is
desde este fin de semana se encuentra
lodging in a hotel near the hospital and
loada en un hotel cercano al hospital y
visits her niece and the little soul every day
visita cada día a su sobrina y a la
u I just got a chill family
u Me acaba de dar un escalofrío familia
it's that I with these things about children the
es que yo con estas cosas de los niño la
truth is I get very sensitive
verdad me pongo muy sensible
eh I just got a
eh Me acaba de entrar de recorrer una
thing run through my body man I don't know how to
cosa al cuerpo tío No sé
explain it to you I don't know how to explain it to you the
explicaros no sé cómo explicaros la
truth these
verdad estas
things this is now no no these videos
cosas esto es ahora no no estos vídeos
are archive
son archivo
no This is not now
no Esto no es ahora
man they are
hombre son fotos de
archive photos Let's see María del Monte what she
archivo A ver María del monte qué ha
said a lot of sense So she was
dicho mucho sentido Entonces ella estuvo
on Saturday with Isabel Pantoja
el sábado de Isabel Pantoja llegaron más
the others arrived later the children and so on and on
tarde los demás los hijos y demás y el
Sunday they were eh María well María
domingo estuvieron eh María bueno María
del Monte is  close to the Pantoja family
del monte es cercana a familia Pantoja
no I don't know what relationship she has specifically
no no sé qué relación tiene en concreto
with Anabel I don't know if you can tell me something
con Anabel no sé si me sabéis decir algo
the children who have less problems
los hijos que tienen menos problemas de
coinciding Kiko and Isa But Isabel Pantoja
coincidir Kiko e Isa Pero Isabel Pantoja
at this moment maybe there would be many
en este momento a lo mejor habría muchas
things to talk about and a separate hospital
cosas que hablar y un hospital aparte
that they are in the is in the u I am
que están en la está en la u Yo estoy
with María in this eh What's going on Are these
con María en esto eh Qué pasa esto Son
real images that are coming
imágenes de verdad las que están
out here yes no This yes no This yes no I mean
saliendo aquí si no Esto sí no Esto sí
this one of Kiko arriving
no O sea esta de Kiko llegando
surely yes
seguramente sí
no these images and true Look
no estas imágenes y verdadera Mira
explaining
explicando
perfectly per Maybe it's not the
perfectamente per Quizá no es la
situation to talk about it let's see but if I do
situación para hablarlo a ver pero si yo
n't say
no
open in a moment we learn little
dig abra en un moment aprendemos poco
because Look due to a misfortune everyone has come to the
porque Mira por una desgracia ha acudido
same place well the
todo el mundo al mismo punto bien las
misfortunes we don't realize that here we are
desgracias no nos damos cuenta que aquí
to leave anyone any
estamos para irnos cualquiera cualquier
day and at any moment [ __ ] Yes how
día y en cualquier momento [__] Sí qué
important this
importante esto
eh what a
eh que
marquise Sorry man I didn't mean for you to
marquesa Perdona hombre no quería que te
get like that sweetheart Sorry daughter I was
pusieras así corazón Perdona hija me he
wrong It's that I'm a lot of people daughter
equivocado Es que soy mucha gente hija
I'm a lot of people and and there is a person who
soy mucha gente y y hay una persona que
is on WhatsApp with the same name
está por WhatsApp con el mismo nombre
as you and then I thought it was you
que tú y entonces me creía que era tú
damn it was too much of a coincidence is that you
[__] era mucha casualidad es que has
said something
dicho algo
similar a kiss  a round of applause for the whole chat
parecido un beso un aplauso todo el chat
for Marquise, man, we are
para marquesa hombre que estamos
sensitive with the news and man, let's
sensibles con la noticia y hombre vamos
cheer up a little bit,
a animarnos un poquillo
ma'am, it's just not an appropriate time,
señora es que no es un momento apropiado
ideal time to give each other a hug, to
idóneo para darse un abrazo totalmente
melt together and pour out that thing
para fundirse y derramar eso que se
called love instead of resentment, even if it
llama amor en lugar de rencor que Aunque
ends, it's the same, it has nothing to do with it
acabe es lo mismo no tiene nada que ver
and perhaps when that hug happens, there will
y quizás cuando ese abrazo se produzca
be something very important
habrá algo importantísimo
Nacho Yes,
Nacho Sí
yes, I do believe that in this life we ​​are here to
sí yo creo que sí que en esta vida
go and in the end, the
estamos para irnos y al final cuantas
more bad experiences it brings you and you're angry, it's
más malas experiencias te lleve y está
true, your family is
enfadado espanada verdad familia está
angry, those things are not at all, true, it
enfadado esas cosas para nada verdad que
's an internal force in the heart that will
es una fuerza interna en el corazón que
help you cope with things
ayudará a sobrellevar las cosas de otra
differently, whatever the end may be, I don't care,
manera fuere cuá fuere el final me da
nice message, I liked it, I
igual bonito mensaje me ha gustado me ha
really liked it, there's nothing else, guys, it's just that there isn't any news, let's
mucho que no hay más nada chicos es que
see, I would like to see what
no hay novedades a ver querría ver lo
Marta said, let's see if someone
que ha dicho Marta a ver si alguien lo
has
ha
posted it, I think if each Spaniard gave a peseta,
puesto pienso si una peseta diera cada
but not to me, where do they have to, well,
español pero no a m a donde tienen que
today she's launching the challenge so they can
bueno hoy estrena el reto para que
talk, the damned ones are very
hablen Los malditos que están muy
worried about my economy, calm down,  I'm
preocupados p mi economía tranquilos que
not hungry haha
no paso hambre jaj
Sister Well if there's any news
Sor Bueno si hay Alguna novedad ahora
we'll be back now
volveremos